st-clair.net 2016-11-22

# Privacy - St. Clair CDS Board

> ##### Privacy Policy
> 
> We recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by the St. Clair Catholic District School Board, including www.st-clair.net.
> 
> If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at
> 
> Privacy Officer  
>  St. Clair Catholic District School Board  
>  420 Creek Street,  
>  Wallaceburg, Ontario, N8A 4C4
> 
> ##### Information we collect and how we use it
> 
> In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:
> 
> _**Information you provide**_ – When you sign up for a Site Account or other service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). 
> 
> _**Cookies**_ – When you visit our sites, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, so that the sites can recognize you as the same user as you go from page to page.
> 
> _**Log information**_ – When you access our sites, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
> 
> _**User communications**_ – When you send email or other communications to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.
> 
> _**Links**_ – we may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our content.
> 
> _**Other sites**_ – This Privacy Policy applies to St. Clair Catholic District School Board services only. We do not exercise control over other sites or advertisements linked from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.
> 
> We do not sell or share the information we collect with third parties except where required under applicable laws.
